A Guide to the Richmond Renaissance Inc. Archives, 1956-1995
Virginia Commonwealth University, James Branch Cabell Library
- Education
  - Citizen's Report: A Strategic Plan for Richmond's Future (Box A36)
  - Richmond Tomorrow: Community Assessment 1990 (Box A36)
  - Water Management-James River and Kanawha Canal 1993 (Box A36)
  - City of Downtown Riverfront Study Group 1986-1987 (Box A36)
  - South of the James September 30, 1986 (Box A36)
  - 7th Street Fountain 1992-1993 (Box A36)
  - Canal Walk/Brown's Island Improvements 1986-1989 (Box A37)
  - Canal Waterworks A and B 1993 (Box A37)
  - Journal of American Planning Association; Vol. 53 no. 1,2 and 3 (Box A37)
  - Kleos: Excellence in Richmond Business 1989 (Box A37)
  - Main Street Ohio; December 1981 (Box A37)
  - Sixth Street Marketplace Feasibility Study Feb. 10, 1983 (Box A37)
  - Sixth Street Marketplace Sculpture Review (Box A37)
  - 1988 Agenda, December 1987 (Box A37)
  - Project Reference File (Box A37)
  - For A Change; October: Vol. 1 No. 13 1988 (Box A37)
  - Shockoe Bottom Revitalization Plan; February 1983 (Box A37)
  - Housing Credit Study; September 1991 (Box A37)
  - Economic Impact of a Proposed Regional Visitor Orientation and Information Center in the Richmond, Virginia Metro Region Nov. 14, 1985 (Box A37)
  - Sixth Street Marketplace Budget 1989 (Box A37)
  - The Chicago Project: A Report on Civic Life in Chicago; September 1986 (Box A37)
  - Committee Report to the Richmond Renaissance Executive Committee; September 1986 (Box A37)
  - Findings of Broad and Grace Street Retail District Analysis April 1, 1986 (Box A37)
  - Richmond Renaissance: A Public Approach Feb. 7, 1983 (Box A37)
  - Request for Design-Build Proposal: New Visitor Orientation Center Feb. 2, 1987 (Box A37)
  - Richmond Architectural Renovation (Box A37)
  - Richmond Historical Theaters (Box A37)
  - Richmond Riverfront Concept Plan (Box A37)
  - The Richmond Canals: A Conceptual Master Plan March 22, 1988 (Box A37)
  - Jackson Ward Vision 2000: Technical Report; May 1988 (Box A37)
  - Richmond's Something Else (Box A37)
  - Virginia Record; Nov/Dec 1988 (Box A37)
  - Richmond Celebrates! (Box A37)
  - June Jubilee: The Tenth Anniversary Celebration 1986 (Box A37)
  - Research Parks, Universities and Industry: Conference; May 1989 (Box A37)
  - Business Properties; Summer 1989 (Box A37)
  - Richmond Surroundings; April/May 1989 (Box A37)
  - Richmond Commercial Real Estate Market Review 1989 (Box A37)
  - The Richmond Traveler; April/May 1989 (Box A37)
  - Virginia Business; April 1989 (Box A37)
  - American Visions; June 1986 (Box A37)
  - Downtown Richmond Planning Maps (Box A38)
  - Leadership Metro Richmond Directory 1981-1987 (Box A38)
  - Economic and Market Analysis Northside Revitalization Study Richmond, Virginia; August 1980 (Box A38)
  - Informational Summary Brochure for the Northside Commercial Area (Box A38)
  - A Commercial Revitalization Plan for the Second Street Commercial Area Richmond, Va; March 1981 (Box A38)
  - Visitor Orientation and Information Center: Summary Statement May 12, 1986 (Box A38)
  - The Temple: Robert Winthrop-Architect (Box A38)
  - City-Wide Survey of Attitudes and Opinions Regarding DowntownMarch 31, 1983 (Box A38)
  - The National Endowment for the Arts: Planning to Make the Arts Basic 1991 (Box A38)
  - Downtown Plan (Box A38)
  - A Proposal for A Public Relations Program for Richmond Renaissance February 7, 1983 (Box A38)
  - Going for the Goal Projects: Virginia Commonwealth Department of Psychology (Box A38)
  - Report on the Capital City Government Commission June 29, 1981 (Box A38)
  - Retail Market Analysis: Downtown Richmond; July 1990 (Box A38)
  - The One to One Partnership, Inc.: Pathways Initiative (Box A38)
  - Finding of Broad Street Retail Analysis April 1, 1986 (Box A.8)
  - Project 1: area Parking Study March 1, 1983 (Box A38)
  - 17th Street Farmers Market Renewal Plan October 31, 1985 (Box A38)
  - A Revitalization Plan for the Second Street Business District Area; December 1983 (Box A38)
  - A Proposed Stategy for Organizing, Staffing and Funding a Renaissance in Tourism and Convention (Box A38)
  - Development in the Richmond, Virginia Area September 15, 1982 (Box A38)
  - Glenn Monigle and Associate, inc.: Richmond Area Signage Program (Box A38)
  - Loan Application Proposal-Richmond Downtown Small Business 1983 (Box A39)
  - Richmond Tour Packet (Box A39)
  - BSTF August Cold Call Interviews 1984 (Box A39)
  - Big River Weekend Poster (Riverfront) (Box A39)
  - Broad Street Photos, oversize
  - Plays and Community Posters, oversize
  - Newsletter Layouts, oversize
  - Canal Walk Drawings, oversize